He was not on the list.
I had guessed that kind of guest.
How does it feel after being eleven times that the program is now closed down?
It feels very boring.
Generally, there is too little specific stock.
It's a pretty good focus here.
Everything from specific corporate cases and managers-
-To little more general stock exchange, market prospects.
It is generally high ceilings and good substances.
And good guests.
One reason you have been allowed to come back-
-Is that the programs have been immensely popular.
If you look back, what kind of favorite memories do you have?
During the pandemic when it was at its most turbulent on the market-
-There it was very exciting.
Then it happened so much.
It was about market prospects for some year.
May have been 2022.
I was a little more hesitant and he was pretty positive.
He is always.
I think it was I who led the section.
I remember it went very well.
There were at least 20,000-30,000 viewers.
You're something on the track.
We must take the opportunity to take the temp for the new year.
But before we do that we need to look back-
-And get the stock exchange perspective on these years.
What has happened?
It has been a very exciting period.
The pandemic has set the tone for what has happened.
Partly in the beginning when we had the strong stock market fall ...
-And that you should build a stock portfolio that you can live on.
I'm not fire.
I am for living and having a good time.
No, I'm not Fire, but I'm saving a lot.
I've always done that.
I like to work.
I love my job.
I like to work on.
We have looked back at all the exciting things that have happened.
But we have to take the opportunity to take the temp on the coming year-
-and hear your thoughts.
The program will be the most viewed for 2024.
You can hope.
I think 2024 will also be an exciting year.
Now I think we put the period of two years of high and rising inflation-
-And interest rate hikes from the central banks behind us.
-temafonds and sector funds ...
The return that the investment provides is not at all the same as investors receive.
The majority of investors come in late and are down.
So the theme can look great out-
-But for many it will not be.
They come in too late.
But if you have such things, you should keep it.
After all, there is a huge need to replace fossil fuels and electrify.
Then we have seen a large AI rally on the stock exchange.
But it is narrow, it is the big US giants that have passed.
But then there is a second wave in this, when other companies that are not directly winners-
-And that does not manufacture the semiconductors in software ...
When you see companies absorb the technology, implement it-
I'm one.
That's my guess.
-There you see.
Pallet site anyway.
-Really.
You have made many good programs.
-And ARA ... -85!
-You are an institution!
-I have done over a hundred pieces ...
One, two, three, a nice figure.
A fanfare on it, huh?
-Ases, what many programs.
-You've done more than ...
If anyone has come and has not gone, it is you.
-As I said, they get to go away.
-How does it feel?
I didn't think there were so many.
Maybe over a hundred.
-Lite less than half.
-It feels good to have been able to.